Arduino relate things are found in this directory

"Main" contains some test experiments with sensors and actuators that will be used.
*Everything is still under testing*

ToDo:
	- Replace stepper motor with a servo, as stepper motor cannot  detect its own position


Sources:
	- Ultrasonic sensor uses code from NewPing Library:
		AUTHOR/LICENSE: Tim Eckel - teckel@leethost.com
		Copyright 2016 License: GNU GPL v3 http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl.html
